# CAICK ANDRADE DIAS

I have a passion for solving challenging problems, exploring new ideas and diving into prominent tech stacks. I'm sociable, an effective collaborator and a fast learner. I started my coding journey in college at 17 years old. I have designed, developed and successfully launched a mobile app to solve group bill splitting at restaurants.

in linkedin.com/in/caick-andrade/

github.com/caickdias/

+55 38 99128 0415

Email: caickandrade0@gmail.com Blog: caickdias.github.io/

### **SKILLS SUMARY:**

2 years of experience writing HTML/CSS and JavaScript, ReactJS (React Native) and associated web frameworks).

<u>Technologies:</u> Javascript ES6, Typescript, Node, Socket.io, resp API, React (hooks, contextAPI, async/await, react-router-dom, hook-form, chartjs), React Native (Expo, dev client, mlrkit OCR, React Navigation), git, Github, shell programming, HTML/CSS (TailwindCSS, Bootstrap). Figma, Adobe Suite (Illustrator, After Effects).

### **EXPERIENCE**

Indie Software Developer (2020 - Present) - Divide aí!

- Fully designed, developed and released a fully functional mobile app for both iOS and Android platforms (link below)
- App created using React Native, React and Javascript concepts as React Hooks, Context API, declarative paradigms, functional components, ES6, componetization

Projects and quality diretor (2013 - 2014) - Junior Information Systems Enterprise at UNIMONTES

- Planning and development of internal time clock system using Codelgniter, PHP, jQuery, MySQL and MVC
- Team developent with kanban and Github

## **PROJECTS**

Divide ai! (https://linktr.ee/divideai): mobile app for splitting group bills

Alarm clock: an alarm clock where you have to solve given equation to turn it off

**URL Parser:** paste your URL and the app will parse its information

Invoice generator: generate invoices PDF with node

<u>Shell script static site:</u> a shell script to generate a static HTML website

GoDev discord bot: a bot that will send beecrowd exercises when asked to

**Pokemon API:** app to fetch pokemon's api

Memory game: simple React Native memory game

**Blaze crash scrap:** web scraping with puppeteer for game values

#### **EDUCATION**

**B.Sc. in Information Systems -** Universidade Estadual de Montes Claros (2012-2018)